Love is our shared truth.
Peace is our eternal hope.
We have to pray for this war
so that the war can end quickly
and that everyone can live in harmony.
We must not look for peace from conflicts.
We should look for peace from sharing.
We should respect the value of existence,
embrace everyone's space,
and share everyone's achievements.
This is the way we feel about each other.
We, the religious people, work together
to pray for this war
so that this pain does not happen
and we can return to normal quickly.
Only when we find peace can we turn back.
How do we start from the ecosystem?
If the ecosystem has power, this will be solved.
It is impossible without power.
If the ecosystem has power, everyone knows.
We have to live.
We have to protect the Earth.
If we want the Earth, we have to protect everyone.
In this day and age,
when values are mixed,
a lot of people are worried or anxious.
I would like to introduce our former prophet,
President Nelson Nelson.
He used Jesus Christ as an example to encourage us.
He said,
I wish you all
to use good words to persuade each other
to fight and provoke.
Use understanding to replace hostility.
Use peace to replace conflict.
The survivor is Jesus Christ.
He is the head of this church.
We are his servants.
He will help us to become his messengers of peace.
I witness this in the name of Jesus Christ. Amen.
Peace be upon you.
May the Lord's peace be upon you.
In accordance with the will of Jesus Christ,
in accordance with the rules he made for us,
we will naturally attain peace.
Jesus Christ created so many different ethnicities,
different cultures, different ethnic groups.
He did not decide who is superior and who is inferior.
He decided to follow the rules of this world
in accordance with the rules of this world.
In the end, he was regarded as a superior person.
Of course, in this world,
no one can judge that a person is superior to another.
Therefore, there must be a consensus between human beings
so that we can coexist,
live in harmony,
and eventually attain peace.
As religion, especially the Orthodox Church,
says that God is love,
not has emotion,
exists as coexistence,
the Father, the Son, and the Holy Spirit.
And as God exists,
it's the coexistence that makes existence,
calls us to coexist,
to exist because you exist,
not because of me.
And you are my life, and you are my salvation.
The religious leaders, if we want to be honest,
cannot exercise political power,
cannot have political positions,
because peace is not only we don't fight.
Peace, by that way, is in a prison.
Peace means human rights,
freedom,
at least some freedom and respect
in the human being,
in the human rights.
We must be very honest,
because if we exercise the human rights,
it's a very important thing.
Shalom, shalom means in Hebrew, hello,
it also means greeting,
and it also means peace,
and the way which peace could be attained
is if people would understand
and realize that God is watching over us,
and he cares about us,
and we're all his children,
no matter what is our religion,
and no matter what is our background,
what country we live in,
what language we speak,
everyone are God's children,
and he created us and put us in this world
in order to make the world a better place,
to be rectified, to elevate the world.
And in that spirit,
we all, all human beings,
are equal to that part.
Everyone understands that we,
as long as we understand that we are
creatures created by God
for the purpose of making the world a better place,
we can get along with each other.
There's no room and no place
and no idea for people
to start getting involved
in matters of bloodshed
and in wars and so on.
I would like to extend our wishes
and our hope and prayer
that the world will be
what it's supposed to be,
that the purpose in which it was created
will be fulfilled.
When we live in the human world,
we need to pay special attention
to the harmony between
all beings and all things.
And this kind of harmony
is the eternal truth of the universe.
When we have love in our hearts,
when we think about other things around us,
it also needs to have
a little love and care
that we give to it
and when we give it
special attention,
it also needs to have
a special relationship
that is harmonious with each other.
We need to love each other
with our own hearts.
If there is a war,
it will definitely create a social chaos.
What's important is that
the conflict between a country and a country
and the family
will be destroyed.
Everyone will be separated
from their loved ones
and even those who are alive will die.
So it will be a tragedy.
Last week,
we held a meeting
for the peace of religion
to pray for world peace.
We are also willing
to connect
different religions
and to persuade
to move towards peace
and to move forward.
When the society is in chaos,
the first religion came out,
the 24th religion,
and it called for
different religions
to pray for peace
in Misha.
In Misha, there is a belief
that we should pray for peace,
for the peace of the Middle East.
Everyone needs to have
this motivation.
Only peace can make us happy.
If there is no peace,
there will be no
happiness.
We call for
different religions
to pursue peace,
to seek peace,
to seek peace.
This is a common feature.
We should all work together
in this direction
to seek peace.
We should all pray
for peace
and seek peace.
You